Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
The fire...!
Undo your Paralysis Technique, Raizo!
We will both perish!
Get out of here!
Aye!
Damn, it's scorching!
Aye...
Scorching enough to kill a man!
Hey, look!
Watch out!
The ceiling's going to collapse!
We're doomed!
You're Jinbe, from the Straw Hat crew!
You're incredible!
The fire has yet to spread that way!
Save yourselves!
Aye! We're in your debt!
Don't go dying yourself!
Aye. Go, now!
Got it!
Everybody, on the double!
Yeah!
Why has the fire spread like this?
Dying in battle is one thing...
...but there will be many more
charred dead from the blaze itself!
It's too dangerous to be here...
We'd best get some distance from here.
Dr. Chopper?
What the blazes...?!
I turned back!
Good for you, Doctor!
The side effects from the
extended gigantification have passed!
Yeah!
I didn't expect to turn into a baby
and an old man at the same time...
The effects are great,
but so are the risks.
And those strong side effects
made me smaller and weaker.
Strong, unpredictable
side effects?
Miyagi...
I'm worried about Zoro.
Yes, because of the drug, right?
He had around 20 to 30 broken bones,
on top of being bruised and battered...
In exchange for
the temporary super healing,
he'll suffer twice
as much as he did before, right?
Y-Yes!
Twice as bad as the serious injuries
that immobilized him...
Zoro...
Don't go dying on us!
Who the hell're you?!
H-Hey...
What's going on? I can't...
...move my body!
Don't do it... Stop...!
Don't!
Outta the waaaay!
Where the hell'd you
wander off to, Zoro?!
Dammit!
Why's one of Whitebeard's
commanders here?!
And why's he helping those
stupid newbies?!
let them get the better of me...
Grunts they may be,
they are still Animal Kingdom Pirates.
Kiku... Kin'emon...
I hope you were able to
escape without issue.
Cipher Pol!
Indeed, we are Aigis Zero.
We knew you were here, but...
Let's pretend we
never saw each other, Izo.
We are in no position to ignore
what remains of the Whitebeard Pirates...
...for committing a historical crime.
But for now, our business is
with the Straw Hats alone.
Until we meet again, elsewhere.
No. Wait...
...CP-0!
Yamato
Must reach...
must reach in time!
There it is!
And thus shall all...
...be led unto their graves.
No, no!
Wait, I beg of you!
Namuji...
...Glacier Fang!
If this much gunpowder
were to explode,
all would be lost!
You will not make contact
with the gunpowder!
Mahoroba!
Orochi-sama!
Stop it, Big Mom!
Our bosses can't move anymore!
If they take any more than they already have,
they'll die for real!
Give 'em a break, already!
Pity from your underlings...
Your reputation's going down the drain!
C'mon, stat!
Boss! Stay with us!
Is he even breathing?!
Save the captain, medics!
Shut up!
This is a battlefield,
you garbage!
God of Lightning, Tenjin!
I'll burn all the garbage,
burnable or not!
That reminds me...
I haven't heard Kaido give
his shout of victory yet.
Don't tell me you're still fooling around
with that half-pint Straw Hat,
Kaido!
Hera!
Take us to the rooftop!
Yes, Mama!
I'm positively pooped!
Let's finish 'em all in one sitting!
Turning your back
on the battlefield...
Kroom:
Anesthesia!
Let's wrap this up!
Mama!
Big Mom's dead!
Traf!
What's with that ginormous sword?!
I know it was effective last time.
There's no pain from the penetration.
But...
Sth... Sthop!
Yuh're gonnuh...
Shock Wille!
Mama?!
How dare you do that to Mama!
What the...?!
I'm being pulled!
Stupid ass loudmouthed
steel beams!
My magnetism rules you!
Still standing, Kid?
You want my head that badly, do ya...
Damn babies!
For some reason, I feel like some other purpose
is driving me right now...
I'm guessin' Kaido up there's
about done, too...
Even dripping water
can hollow out a stone over time.
No damage?
Ain't nothin' in this world
that don't take damage!
Punk Corna Dio!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
It's bigger than the gigantified Big Mom!
Hey!
Listen up, grandma...
You'll get to the rooftop...
...over our dead bodies!
It moves!
It is moving backward!
Must keep it as far away
from the capital as possible...
will not let...
...this thing crash
into the capitaaaal!
Someone... calls for me?
He sent Big Mom flying!
Big Mom isn't down
for the count, is she?
Boss Kid!
He did it!
Yay!
Yes!
Captain!
Feelin' it now, ya gross hag?!
Hey, Eustasser.
That's the second time!
You showed me up by throwing out that attack
after my big ability, then acted like you won by yourself!
I'm not your damn opening act!
Who the hell cares?!
Keep yer dumb to yourself!
How about you
take the lead next, then?
Go on, give her a good slug!
Then I'll come in and finish the job!
Don't tell me what to do!
I'm killin' the old fart
with my badass-est attack!
Oh, what comes after the bull?
A hippo? An elephant?
Shaddap! I told ya,
Jain't showin' you what's up my sleeve!
Captain...
He's 'boutta get hit for talking smack
about our boss like that!
Hey, over there!
Those shockwaves inside me...
Feels like I cracked some ribs, too.
Trafalgar's technique is a real threat.
I think she likes my technique.
Don't be so fulla yourself, asshat!
give you life...
Come back to life,
bones of mine!
Yes, Mama!
So here's something
that isn't a joke...
The next round's gonna
use up all I've got left.
So I'm ending it with the next pass
we make at her.
And I won't miss.
So I'm gonna need you to...
just told you to
not tell me what to do!
Prometheus!
Napoleon!
Hera! Let's do it!
Yes, Mama!
I can keep knocking you back all day!
Maser Saber!
Joke's on you!
It was scrap metal to begin with!
The joke's on you two!
Idiot brats!
I've sent hundreds of
punks like you to the seabed!
We've reigned for decades...
...before you twerps...
...were weaned off your mothers' milk!
Assign!
S!
CON!
Hnaa?!
Run, Mama!
I'm stuck!
Huuuh?!
She moved the whole tower to block?!
You senile old ass hag!
You unruly brat...
Know your place!
Mother's Visit Cannon:
3,000 Leagues of Misery!
You can't run from me!
What the hell?!
Her attack came to life?!
Get them, Misery!
Flatten those br-
Takt!
Mama?!
Kroom:
Anesthesia!
Again with that trick, Trafalgar?!
What is that?!
Damn you!
You've got guts, boy!
Think you're not gonna let go,
eh, Trafalgar?!
Captain!
What're you doing, Captain?!
Let go! You're gonna die!
Not yet! Go deeper!
What's wrong, dead already?!
Puncture...
Nuh?! Don't do it!
Wille!
Eh?!
What is that giant hole?!
Hah?!
What?! A hole, here?!
Fry him to a crisp, Misery!
Yes, Mama!
Do it, Eustasser!
Nwuh?!
What's this?!
Don't make me
repeat myself, Trafalgar!
Don't tell me what to do!
You damned pups!
Come on, boy!
You think you can take me down?!
I'm Big Mom!
That's exactly why I gotta murder ya!
Damned Punk!
Your era...
is over!
You two think...
...you're soooo clever!
Say there, runts!
You must really, really like me!
You've gotta be at the end
of your little act, though, hmm?
You probably thought
you drove me into a corner,
but in the end you couldn't
put the final nail in the coffin.
You can't win against me.
Why?! Why hasn't she been
blasted away yet?!
Even a blitz like that won't kill her?!
No way!
Both of our guys've capped out!
What's gonna become of you once I've
knocked away your attack?
You decide!
Forfeit fifty years of your lifespans...
...or live, and become my slaves!
Life...
or...
...Slaves!
That's her Soul Pocus!
Boss, let's find a way outta here!
She's taking our lifespans too!
No, no, no!
Oh, no!
Don't do it, dammit!
A dying creature
shouldn't be that powerful!
I'm scaaaared!
Captain! We've gotta get
distance from here!
What?!
Take your own advice.
Quit yer screechin'!
Give up my lifespan?
Become your slave?
Don't make me laugh.
Why the hell would some one-foot-in-the-grave
granny's chanting freak me out?!
They haven't lost a single second
of their lifespans!
Are they not the least bit afraid
of an Emperor of the Sea?!
Re-Room...
Your death rattle would probably
make my ears bleed.
In that case...
This is something my savior would do.
You just don't know when to give up,
huh, Empress of the Sea?
How bout I give you a hand...
...and send you to hell!
...Silent!
Huh? The sound's all gone!
Silent....
This technique cancels out
any and all noise created by you.
Can't hear you...
What is this?!
My voice... I can't speak!
Mama!
Captain, behind you!
Here's my follow-up!
Damned Punk!
Mama!
Prometheus!
Hera!
What are you doing?!
Help your Mama!
What?! Big Mom?!
Why can I not hear her?
Nothing I touch makes a sound!
What have you done to me, Trafalgar!!
Stop!
You will cause a chain reaction!
Orochi-sama...!
Eh?!
What is happening?!
Damn it all!
It all started with that...!
Hey, Roger...
Why did you have to
go and say that?
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it...
Go, find it!
I've left everything
this world's got to offer there!
The whole world bought it!
"Great Pirate Era"?
Roger....
You didn't care since you were
already a dead man!
But when those kids rise up
all over the world...
...we're the ones that have to clean up
that damn mess of runts you left behind!
What the...? What's going on?!
What happened?!
Is anyone there?!
Answer me!
Waaaateeeer!
You hear me, Roger?
You should've told us
before you died!
The One Piece...
Is it real?
It better be!
What is it?
Where is it?
Some of it's in
this country too, isn't it?!
Gaaah, I'm so close!
Kid!
Law!
They'll both pay!
Damn it all!
Don't even think for a second...
Not one second...
...that this'll kill me!
Empress of the Sea Big Mom versus
the New Generation,
at the Battle of the Performance Floor,
Skull Dome Interior.
The victors:
Yahoo!
We won!
Eustass "Captain" Kid...
...and...
"Surgeon of Death" Trafalgar Law.
Boss!
Captain!
We beat Big Mom!
This is a huge deal!
Really huge!
Do not tell me...
You are...!
So it is you!
Right!
This will do, for now!
Nice! Keep going, Momonosuke-kun!
Ah, 'tis you, Yamato!
Is that the basement?!
My word!
Tis exposed!
Indeed it is!
One of the bombs exploded,
and this is the result!
So the explosion earlier
was caused by Big Mom?!
Aye. I managed to freeze everything
before the whole armory exploded!
I see.
I am glad to see you well!
As I am occupied at the moment,
I ask you pay heed to what I say...
As we speak, it is nearing us...
Zunesha!
Is that the elephant Oden
mentioned in his journal?!
Indeed!
The very companion of Joyboy,
and the culprit behind a crime eight hundred years ago!
If we aim for a new world,
We have no choice but to break through here
yoku wo kaita kenryoku-sha
The greedy, and the powerful
no-nonsense scum will turned the world upside down
Remember my face,
and the prize on my neck.
It's constantly being renewed
It's a good deal isn't it? If only you can beat me...
Tomorrow's NEWS will always
comes from here
shin jidai kake nukeru HEADLINERS
running through the new era HEADLINERS
kono sekai noshi agare BADLINERS
rise to the top of this world HEADLINERS
SUPERNOVA is on the verge of a breakthrough
ore ni meirei suru yatsu wa
Anyone who orders me around,
I'll make you disappear
KUUM
Bounty hunters, kidnappers,
a crossroads of rough and tumble furies,
let alone the future, even the way to die
The weak don't always get to choose
hito no yabou warau yatsu wa
Whoever laughs at my ambitions...
hitori nokorazu keshite kita
I will eliminate every single one them
yuugen jikkou hara gime na
I'll do what I say, when I say it
kakugo no nai yatsu ga shinu umi wa sugu
because the sea will soon kill those who are unprepared
Legends of the Future, Yeah
it all starts here
seiryokuzu kaki kaeru FAULINERS
Will rewrite the map of power HEADLINERS
The glittering stage beckons
ou no za ga
the throne of the king
yobu no wa dare
calls to whom?
running through the new era, HEADLINERS
kono sekai noshi agare HEADLINERS
rise to the top of this worldHEADLINERS
kitaichi MAX SUPERNOVA
Expectations max supernova
motto sui yose mita shitai
I want to attract more & satisfy, to fill it up
tomi mo meiyo mo
with riches and with honor
HAND